A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Issue Books, Series 17 FA363
Rockefeller Archive Center
- 1964 Presidential Election, 1959-1964; 1; 9.2 Cubic Feet
  - Volume 40 - Economy - Balance-of-Payments/Government Spending/Inflation, 1959-1964 (Box 16, Folder 91)
    Tab 110 NAR Position on Inflation; Speech, Gresham, Oregon; April 17, 1964 - See Economy - General
    Tab 111 Policy Paper, Inflation, Revised May 8, 1964
  - Volume 41 - Economy - Labor-Management Relations, 1959-1964 (Box 16, Folder 92)
    Tab 112 NAR Statement, South Bend, Indiana, December 13, 1959
    Tab 113 Memorandum, Labor Policies, March 16, 1960 -- memoranda outlining Kennedy administration labor policies.
    Tab 114 Position Paper No. M-5, Labor, prepared by Roswell B. Perkins, June 10, 1960
    Tab 115 Position Paper No. M, Labor-Management Issues, prepared by William J. Isaacson, June 10, 1960
    Tab 116 "A Republican Approach to the Great Issues," The Control of Inflation and the Settlement of Major Strikes, July 11, 1960
    Tab 117 Issues Analysis Notebook, Labor, Fall 1960
    Tab 118 Platform Analysis Notebook, Labor, Fall 1960
    Tab 119 Memorandum, Minimum Wage Bill, May 19, 1961 -- summary of minimum wage bill signed by President Kennedy.
    Tab 120 Background Paper, Railroad Dispute, August 1963
    Tab 121 Questions and Answers for "U.S. News & World Report," Right-to-Work, September 5, 1963 -- specific questions on worker rights posed to NAR as part of interview with the news magazine.
    Tab 122 Questions and Answers for "U.S. News & World Report," Emergency Strikes, September 5, 1963 -- specific questions on labor strikes posed to NAR as part of interview with the news magazine.
    Tab 123 Questions and Answers for Associated Press, Federal Right-to-Work Law, October 17, 1963
    Tab 124 Memorandum, "Right-to-Work" Issue, October 21, 1963
    Tab 125 Memorandum, "Right-to-Work" Issue, October 24, 1963
    Tab 126 Excerpts from Letter of NAR, Right-to-Work Laws, November 6, 1963
    Tab 127 NAR Statement in "Christian Science Monitor," Right to Work Legislation, November 8, 1963
    Tab 128 Summary Position Paper, Labor -- General, December 1963
    Tab 129 Press Kit, Labor, Summarized to January 1, 1964 -- published booklet on NAR position on labor.
    Tab 130 Questions and Answers for California Republican Assembly, "Right-to-Work" Laws, February 27, 1964 -- NAR response to questions on labor issues as posed by California Republican Assembly.
    Tab 131 Kuchel Analysis Vote, Labor-Management Relations, May 12, 1964
    Tab 132 Kuchel Analysis Vote, Minimum Wage, May 12, 1964
    Tab 133 Memorandum Criticism of BMG "Blue Book", Labor Management Relations, June 19, 1964
    Tab 134 Draft Platform Language, Right-to-Work, June 25, 1964
    Tab 135 NAR Submission to Republican Platform Committee, San Francisco, Labor, July 7, 1964
    Tab 136 Platform Planks Submitted by Senator Scott, Collective Bargaining, July 9, 1964
    Tab 137 Background Material on Proposed Plank, Collective Bargaining, July 10, 1964
    Tab 138 Background Memorandum 1958 GOP Election Losses in States with "Right-to-Work" Referenda, July 11, 1964
    Tab 139 Background Memoranda, 1958 Republican Election Losses in States with "Right-to-Work" Referenda on the Ballot, July 12, 1964
    Tab 140 From Minority Views, Submitted by Senator Scott to Republican Platform, "Right-to-Work," July 13, 1964
  - Volume 41 - Economy - Taxation, 1959-1964 (Box 16, Folder 93)
    Tab 141 Position Paper No. L-3, Economic-National, Domestic Public Finance Taxation, prepared by C. Lowell Harriss, February 8, 1960 -- paper written by Professor Harriss of Princeton University.
    Tab 142 Summary Position Paper No. L-3, Economic-National, (Domestic) Public Finance Taxation, prepared by Prof. C. Lowell Harriss, March 7, 1960
    Tab 143 Issues Analysis Notebook, Taxation, Fall 1960
    Tab 144 NAR Statement Taxation, September 6, 1960 -- press release of NAR remarks delivered at the 53th Annual Conference on Taxation of the National Tax Association.
    Tab 145 Current Positions Notebook, Taxation, April 13, 1962
    Tab 146 Revised Position Papers for Meeting with New York GOP Congressional Delegation, Taxation, June 27, 1962
    Tab 147 Memorandum, Kennedy Tax Reduction-Revision Statement, August 13, 1962
    Tab 148 Memorandum, The President's 1963 State of the Union Message, January 16, 1963
    Tab 149 Memorandum, The President's Tax Message, January 24, 1963, January 25, 1963
    Tab 150 NAR Statement, Tax Incentives for Growth and More Jobs Now, March 9, 1963 -- published booklet of NAR statement on taxation.
  - Volume 41 - Economy - Taxation, 1959-1964 (Box 16, Folder 94)
    Tab 151 Current Positions Notebook, Taxation, June 1963
    Tab 152 Rockefeller on the Issues, Incentives for Investment: Tax Policies, Summarized by B. Jones, September 1963
    Tab 153 Summary Position Paper, Taxation, prepared by Arthur Schreiber, September 1963
    Tab 154 Memorandum, Effect of Abolishing Income Tax Progression, September 6, 1963
    Tab 155 Questions and Answers for "U.S. News & World Report," Tax Cut, September 23, 1963 -- specific questions on the economy posed to NAR as part of interview with the news magazine.
    Tab 156 Questions and Answers for Associated Press, Tax Cut, October 17, 1963
    Tab 157 Press Kit, Government Spending and Taxation, Summarized to January 1, 1964 -- published booklet on NAR position on government spending and taxation.
    Tab 158 Questions and Answers for California Republican Assembly, Income Tax, February 27, 1964 -- NAR response to questions on taxation as posed by California Republican Assembly. Tab 159 Excerpt from "Model" Platform, Taxation, June 18, 1964
    Tab 160 NAR Submission to Platform Committee (San Francisco), Taxation, July 7, 1964
  - Volume 42 - Education, 1959-1964 (Box 17, Folder 95)
    Tab 1 NAR Statement, Salem, Oregon, November 14, 1959 -- press release of NAR remarks delivered at Willamette University.
    Tab 2 Background Paper No. M-10, Higher Education, by Homer Babbidge, December 1959
    Tab 3 Background Paper No. M-10a, Elementary and Secondary Education, by Homer Babbidge, January 1960
    Tab 4 Summary Paper, Higher Education, by Homer Babbidge, January 12, 1960
    Tab 5 Summary Paper, Elementary and Secondary Education, by Homer Babbidge, February 3, 1960
    Tab 6 Position Paper No. M-10a, Elementary and Secondary Education, by R. Perkins and B. Jones, June 1960
    Tab 7 Position Paper No. M-10, Higher Education, by R. B. Perkins, June 11, 1960
    Tab 8 Questions and Answers for David Susskind's "Open End", Education, June 12, 1960
    Tab 9 Position Papers for "Open End," Higher Education, June 12, 1960
    Tab 10 Draft Plank for 1960 Republican Convention, Education, Science and Technology, June 19, 1960
    Tab 11 Short Summaries of Position Paper, also used as briefing for "Open End" (June 12, 1960), Elementary and Secondary Education, June 22, 1960
    Tab 12 Short summaries of Position Papers, Higher Education, June 22, 1960
    Tab 13 NAR Statement, Better Education for Americans, July 9, 1960 -- published booklet of NAR statement on education.
    Tab 14 "A Republican Approach to the Great Issues," Education: Proposals for Increase Support, July 1960
    Tab 15 Comparison of Republican and Democratic Platforms (R. B. Perkins Platform Analysis), Education, September 9, 1960
    Tab 16 1960 Campaign Analysis, Education, Fall 1960
    Tab 17 Background Paper, Federal Aid to Schools, February 5, 1961
    Tab 18 Special JFK-NAR Comparison, Background Information on Education, February 1961
    Tab 19 Current Positions Paper, Education, April 16, 1961
  - Volume 42 - Education, 1959-1964 (Box 17, Folder 96)
    Tab 20 Memorandum to NAR from R. B. Perkins, Summary of JFK Proposals in State of the Union Message, 1962, Education, January 18, 1962
    Tab 21 Background Paper, Kennedy Education Program, April 25, 1962
    Tab 22 Current Position Paper, Education, May 9, 1962
    Tab 23 Position Paper for Use with New York Republican Delegation, Education, June 27, 1962
    Tab 24 Current Positions Paper, Integration, July 27, 1962
    Tab 25 Current Positions Paper, Civil Rights -- Education, Revised October 16, 1962
    Tab 26 Current Positions Paper, Education, October 16, 1962
    Tab 27 Background Paper, The President's 1963 Education Program, March 6, 1963
    Tab 28 Current Positions Paper, Education, March 8, 1963
    Tab 29 Background Paper, Record of the Kennedy Administration, 1961-1962, Education, May 3, 1963
    Tab 30 Background Paper, Youth/Education, June 17, 1963
  - Volume 43 - Education, 1961-1964 (Box 17, Folder 97)
    Tab 31 Background Paper, Basic Facts and Trends, Gathered for Research Group by Congressman Frelinghuysen, July 8, 1963 -- materials accumulated by the Reference, Estimates, and Projections Section, Studies and Surveys Branch, Division of Educational Statistics, Bureau of Educational Research and Development, US Department of Health, Education, and Welfare.
    Tab 32 Current Positions Paper, Draft: Civil Rights - Education, Revised July 1963
    Tab 33 Background Material Youth Current Positions Paper, August 1963
    Tab 34 First Draft, Education Policy Paper, by Charles B. Saunders, August 1963 -- paper titled "Strengthening American Education."
    Tab 35 "Rockefeller on the Issues," Education, Summary by B. Jones of NAR Stated Positions, September 1963
    Tab 36 Draft Questions and Answers, "U.S. News & World Report" Interview, Education, September 5, 1963 -- specific questions on education posed to NAR as part of interview with the news magazine.
    Tab 37 Draft Questions and Answers, "U.S. News & World Report" Interview, Federal Aid for Parochial Schools, September 5, 1963 -- specific questions on education posed to NAR as part of interview with the news magazine.
    Tab 38 Outline for "Christian Science Monitor," Education, October 1963
    Tab 39 Draft Statement, Education, for New Hampshire Trip, October 18, 1963
    Tab 40 Background Paper, Goldwater Opposition to Three Major Education Bills, October 27, 1963
    Tab 41 Background Paper, Analysis of Tax Deduction and Tax Credit Bills, October 27, 1963
    Tab 42 NAR Interview, "Christian Science Monitor," Education, November 8, 1963
    Tab 43 Draft Statement, Education, November 22, 1963
    Tab 44 Summary Position Paper, Education, December 1963
    Tab 45 Summary Position Paper, Parochial Schools, December 1963
    Tab 46 Summary Position Paper, Tax Deductions and Credits for Higher Education Expenses, December 1963
  - Volume 43 - Education, 1961-1964 (Box 17, Folder 98)
    Tab 47 Policy Paper, Education, December 10, 1963
    Tab 48 Press Kit, Education, Summarized to January 1, 1964 -- published booklet on NAR position on education.
    Tab 49 Background Information: New Hampshire, Federal Aid to Education, January 1, 1964
    Tab 50 Questions and Answers, Federal Aid to Parochial Schools, January 3, 1964
    Tab 51 Draft Statement, Education, January 14, 1964 -- draft of NAR speech to be delivered at Keene State College, Keene, New Hampshire.
    Tab 52 NAR One-Minute Spot Commercial, Education, January 18, 1964
    Tab 53 Speech Card, Parochial Schools, January 25, 1964
    Tab 54 Speech Card, School Prayer, January 25, 1964
    Tab 55 NAR Draft Letter, Aid to Church Schools, February 1964
    Tab 56 NAR Draft Letter, Parochial Schools, February 3, 1964
    Tab 57 Background Paper, NAR Scholarship Program, Cost-of-Education Grants, February 5, 1964
    Tab 58 Background Paper, NAR Scholarship Program, A Federal Program of Student Financial Aid, February 5, 1964
    Tab 59 Background Paper, The Rockefeller Family's Contributions to Education, February 12, 1964
    Tab 60 NAR Radio and Television Spots, Education, February 26, 1964
    Tab 61 NAR Statement, Education, February 29, 1964 -- press release of NAR statement delivered at Laconia, New Hampshire.
    Tab 62 Background Information: California, California Statistics on Education March 1964
    Tab 63 A Comparison on Domestic Issues of Taft, Rockefeller, and Goldwater, Education, April 1964 -- campaign brochure outlining positions held by Senator Robert A. Taft (R-Ohio), Senator Barry Goldwater (R-Arizona), and NAR.
    Tab 64 Fact Sheet, Higher Education in Oregon, April 15, 1964
    Tab 65 Fact Sheet, Elementary and Secondary Education, April 16, 1964
  - Volume 43 - Education, 1961-1964 (Box 17, Folder 99)
    Tab 66 NAR Statement, Corvallis, Oregon, April 17, 1964 -- press release of NAR remarks delivered at Oregon State University.
    Tab 67 NAR Statement, California Newspaper Publishers' Association, Sacramento, California, April 28, 1964
    Tab 68 Conscience of a Republican, Education for the Young, April 28, 1964
    Tab 69 NAR Statement, Beckley, West Virginia, April 30, 1964
    Tab 70 Fact Sheet, Higher Education, May 1964
    Tab 71 Platform Analysis Notebook, Education, May 1964
    Tab 72 "Rockefeller and Our Schools," May 5, 1964 -- published booklet on NAR record in education.
    Tab 73 Nelson Rockefeller and Our Colleges, May 5, 1964 -- published booklet on NAR record in education.
    Tab 74 Answers to "The Monitor" Questionnaire, Elementary and Secondary Education, May 7, 1964 -- selected education questions posed to NAR by the California Catholic newspaper.
    Tab 75 Evaluation of Kuchel Survey of Goldwater Votes, Education, May 9, 1964
    Tab 76 "As A Republican, I Believe... " Education for the Young, May 11, 1964 -- section pertaining to education from published brochure of NAR positions on issues affecting the United States and the Republican Party.
    Tab 77 Background Paper, Analysis of Impact of Goldwater Votes on California, May 15, 1964
    Tab 78 Draft Statement, 1964 GOP Platform, Education, June 4, 1964
    Tab 79 Draft Policy Statement, Education June 17, 1964
    Tab 80 Draft NAR "Model" Platform, Education, June 19, 1964
    Tab 81 Evaluation of Goldwater "Blue Book," Education, June 19, 1964
    Tab 82 Draft Platform Language, Education, June 25, 1964
    Tab 83 Background Paper, Goldwater and Federal Aid to Education, June 30, 1964
    Tab 84 Draft "One Page" Planks, Education, June 30, 1964
    Tab 85 Possible Insertions in Platform, Education, July 1, 1964
    Tab 86 Revised Set of Platform Planks, Education, July 6, 1964
    Tab 87 NAR Presentation to the Platform Committee, Education, July 7, 1964
    Tab 88 Proposed Plank and Background Material on Proposed 12 Planks, Education, July 10, 1964
    Tab 89 General Statement of Minority Views to 1964 GOP Platform, Education, July 13, 1964
    Tab 90 William W. Scranton Statement, "I Take My Stand," Education, July 12, 1964
  - Volume 44 - Federal-State Relations, 1961-1964 (Box 18, Folder 100)
    Tab 1 Memorandum, Program to Strengthen State and Local Governments, February 27, 1963 -- internal memo expanding on themes advanced by NAR in the Godkin lectures, Harvard University, 1962.
    Tab 2 Position Paper, The Federal System -- A Program for Action
    Tab 3 "Rockefeller on the Issues," The Federal System, Summary by B. Jones of NAR Stated Positions, September 1963
    Tab 4 NAR Remarks, Annual Meeting, American Political Science Association, New York city, September 4, 1963
    Tab 5 Draft Questions and Answers, "U.S. News & World Report" Interview, Federal-State Relations, September 5, 1963 -- specific questions on federal-state relations posed to NAR as part of interview with the news magazine.
    Tab 6 Memorandum, Federal-State Relations, September 27, 1963 -- notes from meeting with Professor James Maxwell of Clark University.
    Tab 7 Memorandum, Outline of a Proposed Program on Federal-State Relations, October 10, 1963 -- outline prepared in advance of meeting on issue.
    Tab 8 NAR Remarks, League of California Cities, San Francisco, California, October 23, 1963
    Tab 9 Current Positions Notebook, Federal-State Relations, November 14, 1963
    Tab 10 Material Prepared for Meeting with NAR, Federal-State Relations, December 16, 1963 -- NAR suggested positions and background material on federal-state relations.
    Tab 11 Background Paper, Government Spending and the Federal System, December 20, 1963 -- paper written by Professor Maxwell after meeting on December 16.
    Tab 12 Positive One-Minute Spots, Federalism, February 1, 1964
    Tab 13 Memorandum, US Chamber of Commerce Speech, The New Federalism, February 1, 1964 -- Rod Perkins memo on upcoming speech to be delivered at the US Chamber of Commerce.
    Tab 14 Domestic "White Paper" #1, Government Closest to the People, February 19, 1964
  - Volume 44 - Federal-State Relations, 1961-1964 (Box 18, Folder 101)
    Tab 15 NAR Statement, Keeping Government Close to the People, February 27, 1964
    Tab 16 Domestic "White Paper" #1, Government Closest to the People, March 17, 1964
    Tab 17 Background Paper, Shifting Government Financial Resources from the Federal Level to the State-Local Level, March 25, 1964
    Tab 18 Draft Statement, Government Closest to the People, April 9, 1964 -- revision of February 19, 1964 White Paper.
    Tab 19 Domestic "White Paper" #1, Material for Introduction, April 10, 1964
    Tab 20 Memorandum, Explanation of Tax Credit Proposal Suggested in Domestic White Paper #1, April 10, 1964 -- Rod Perkins memo explaining tax credit proposal found in White Paper.
    Tab 21 Background Paper, National Planning Association Projections of State-Local Purchases of Goods and Services, 1962-1973, April 10, 1964 -- projected increases in revenue and goods and services.
    Tab 22 Empty
    Tab 23 NAR Statement, Federalism, April 17, 1964 -- remarks delivered at the City Club of Portland, Oregon.
    Tab 24 Press Kit, The American Federal System, Summarized to January 1, 1964 -- published booklet on NAR position on Federal-State relations.
    Tab 25 Background Paper, Government Close to the People, May 4, 1964
    Tab 26 Answers to "The Monitor" Questionnaire, Federal Relations, May 7, 1964 -- selected federal-state relations questions posed to NAR by the California Catholic newspaper.
    Tab 27 "As A Republican, I Believe... " States Rights and States Responsibilities, May 11, 1964 -- section pertaining to federal-state relations from published brochure of NAR positions on issues affecting the United States and the Republican Party.
    Tab 28 Draft Statement, The Federal System, June 4, 1964
    Tab 29 Draft Statement, "The Quiet Revolution," the Threat to the Future of American Federalism, June 16, 1964
    Tab 30 Memorandum, Governor Romney's Request for Suggestions for his July 8 Platform Committee Testimony, June 17, 1964 -- Rod Perkins memo to NAR with suggested letter to send on Romney's request from Republican governors for language to be used in testimony for the platform.
    Tab 31 Excerpt from "Model" Platform, Federal-State Relations, June 18, 1964
    Tab 32 Excerpt from "Model" Platform, Federal-State Relations, June 18, 1964
    Tab 33 Evaluation of Goldwater "Blue Book," Federalism and States Rights, June 19, 1964
    Tab 34 Position Paper, Walter Heller Position on Routing more Funds to State and Local Governments, June 23, 1964 -- Heller quote from "US News and World Report" article.
    Tab 35 Memorandum, Explanation of Tax Credit Proposal, June 24, 1964
    Tab 36 NAR Presentation to the Platform Committee, Federal-State System, July 7, 1964
  - Volume 45 - Health, General, 1959-1964 (Box 18, Folder 102)
    Tab 1 Background Paper No. M-16, Public Health in the United States, General Health Services, March 3, 1960 -- paper written by Dr. Berwyn Mattison of the American Public Health Association.
    Tab 2 Background Paper No. M-16b, Mental Health, April 26 1960 -- paper written by Dr. Paul Lemkau, of the School of Hygiene and Public Health [Johns Hopkins?].
    Tab 3 Position Paper No. M-16b, Mental Health, April 28, 1960 -- suggested NAR positions as a result of Dr. Lemkau's paper.
    Tab 4 Position Paper No. M-16, Health, June 9, 1960 -- suggested NAR positions as a result of Dr. Mattison's paper.
    Tab 5 Position Papers for "Open End," Health, June 12, 1960
    Tab 6 Short Summaries of Position Papers, Health, June 22, 1960
    Tab 7 RBP Platform Analysis, Health and Welfare, June 22, 1960
    Tab 8 1960 Campaign Analysis, Health, Fall 1960
  - Volume 45 - Health, General, 1959-1964 (Box 18, Folder 103)
    Tab 9 JFK-NAR Comparison, Background Information on Health, Fall 1961
    Tab 10 Memorandum to NAR from R. B. Perkins, Summary of JFK Proposals in State of the Union Message, 1962, Health, January 18, 1962
    Tab 11 Memorandum, Recent Developments in the Food and Drug Field, August 18, 1962 -- memo to NAR as a result of "recent tragedies surrounding the uses of Thalidomide" detailing changes in policies with experimental drugs.
    Tab 12 Current Positions Notebook, Health, October 14, 1962
    Tab 13 Current Positions Paper, Health, General, May 1963
    Tab 14 Current Positions Notebook, Mental Health and Retardation, June 1963
    Tab 15 Draft Policy Paper, Health, July 10, 1963 -- paper written by Dr. Herman Hilleboe.
    Tab 16 Research Report on Proposal for National Committee on Health Manpower, July 18, 1963
    Tab 17 Draft Policy Statement, Health, September 26, 1963
  - Volume 46 - Health, General, 1961-1964 (Box 18, Folder 104)
    Tab 18 Health Professionals Educational Assistance Act of 1963 [H.R. 12], October 21, 1963 -- act to provide assistance for the construction and expansion of medical schools, as well as authorizing loans for medical students.
    Tab 19 Current Positions Paper, Health, General, November 1963
    Tab 20 NAR Interview, "Christian Science Monitor," Health, November 8, 1963
    Tab 21 Summary Position, Health and Welfare, December 1963
    Tab 22 Issue Correspondence, January 2, 1964 -- sample of letter sent to constituents on health issues.
    Tab 23 Material for Mort Frayn letter on Handicapped Children, January 30, 1964
    Tab 24 Issue Correspondence, February 12, 1964 -- sample of letter sent to constituents on mental health issues.
    Tab 25 Memorandum, Johnson's Health Message, February 18, 1964 -- critique of LBJ health proposal submitted to Congress.
    Tab 26 Press Kit, Health, Summarized to May 1, 1964 -- text from published booklet on NAR position on health.
    Tab 27 A Comparison on Domestic Issues of Taft, Rockefeller, and Goldwater, Health, April 1964 -- campaign brochure outlining positions held by Senator Robert A. Taft (R-Ohio), Senator Barry Goldwater (R-Arizona), and NAR.
    Tab 28 Platform Analysis Notebook, Health, May 1964
  - Volume 46 - Health, Medicare, 1959-1964 (Box 18, Folder 105)
    Tab 29 Background Paper No. M-16a, Social Security Legislation, 1960, March 12, 1960 -- paper written by Wilbur J. Cohen, Professor of Public Welfare Administration, University of Michigan.
    Tab 30 Position Paper No. M-16a, Health Insurance for the Aged, June 6, 1960 -- paper written by Rod Perkins.
    Tab 31 Position Papers for "Open End," Health Insurance for the Aged, June 22, 1960
    Tab 32 Short Summaries of Position Papers for "Open End," Health Insurance for the Aged, June 22, 1960
    Tab 33 NAR Statement, Health Care for the Aged, June 29, 1960 -- published booklet of NAR speech delivered at the Governors Conference, Glacier National Park, Montana.
    Tab 34 "A Republican Approach to the Great Issues," Medical Care for Our Senior Citizens, July 1960
  - Volume 46 - Health, Medicare, 1959-1964 (Box 18, Folder 106)
    Tab 35 Memorandum, Javits Health Insurance Bill, April 26, 1961 -- memo to NAR on plan by Senator Javits to introduce a health bill that includes NAR plan for private health insurance.
    Tab 36 Background Paper, Medical Aid to the Aged, September 8, 1961